{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "1+1=?",
      "answers": ["2", "11", "1+1", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "2-1=?",
      "answers": ["21", "12", "1", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "1+8=?",
      "answers": ["18", "81", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "10-1=?",
      "answers": ["110", "101", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "1+3+6=?",
      "answers": ["163", "631", "136", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "6-1-2=?",
      "answers": ["3", "261", "216", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "12+7=?",
      "answers": ["712", "127", "19", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "12-5=?",
      "answers": ["125", "512", "7", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "20-11=?",
      "answers": ["1019", "1910", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "15+4-10=?",
      "answers": ["10154", "15410", "5", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "9+4=?",
      "answers": ["13", "94", "49", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "9-6",
      "answers": ["3", "96", "69", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "3+3+3+3=?",
      "answers": ["3333", "33333", "333", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "29+15=?",
      "answers": ["2915", "9", "44", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "19-5-5=?",
      "answers": ["5195", "5519", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "6-1-2=?",
      "answers": ["216", "261", "3", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "7+2-1=?",
      "answers": ["172", "8", "127", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "8-3+7=?",
      "answers": ["12", "387", "873", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "15-8+1=?",
      "answers": ["8115", "1518", "8151", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "22-5-8=?",
      "answers": ["8522", "5822", "2285", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "13+12-15=?",
      "answers": ["151312", "131512", "151213", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "18-23-87=?",
      "answers": ["871823", "872318", "-92", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "23-14+17=?",
      "answers": ["141723", "231714", "142317", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "15-38+32=?",
      "answers": ["381532", "153832", "383215", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "9+6+13=?",
      "answers": ["28", "32", "9613", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "19-6-3=?",
      "answers": ["9", "10", "3619", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "9+9+9+9+9+9+9=?",
      "answers": ["9999999", "72", "63", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "9-9+9-9+9-9+9",
      "answers": ["9999999", "0", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "2+3+4+5-6-7+8=?",
      "answers": ["7623458", "6723458", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "|15-24|=?",
      "answers": ["2415", "-9", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "|29-20+4|=?",
      "answers": ["13", "20294", "53", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "|59+100-117|=?",
      "answers": ["56", "42", "11759100", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "|1-2-1-2-1-2-1+1|=?",
      "answers": ["121212211", "112122112", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "|1-2-1-2-1+2-1|=?",
      "answers": ["1211212", "1211122", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "|23-15+2|=?",
      "answers": ["15232", "15233", "15223", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "1+4+5+4-3=?",
      "answers": ["31545", "31454", "11", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "5-2-3+6=?",
      "answers": ["3652", "6", "3256", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "27-19=?",
      "answers": ["1927", "2719", "8", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "|5-8|+6=?",
      "answers": ["865", "856", "568", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "17-|8-15|=?",
      "answers": ["15817", "17815", "81517", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "9-6-5=?",
      "answers": ["-2", "-3", "569", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "3+9+7=?",
      "answers": ["21", "19", "397", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "12+1+1+1+1=?",
      "answers": ["1211111", "1111111", "121111", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "15-1-1-1-1-1-1=?",
      "answers": ["11111115", "1111115", "111115", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "7-71-17=?",
      "answers": ["17717", "17177", "17771", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "456-123+78=?",
      "answers": ["45612378", "12345678", "45678123", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "78-456-123=?",
      "answers": ["12378456", "12346578", "12345678", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "123-456+342",
      "answers": ["342123456", "456123342", "342456123", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "321-654-87=?",
      "answers": ["87654321", "87645321", "32165487", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "87+654+321=?",
      "answers": ["87654231", "87654321", "87564321", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "0+0+7=?",
      "answers": ["7", "James Bond", "007", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "0-3+12=?",
      "answers": ["3012", "312", "15", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "7-0-0=?",
      "answers": ["007", "700", "James Bond", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "0+0-0+0-0=?",
      "answers": ["0", "00000", "False", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "|0-1|=?",
      "answers": ["1", "0", "10", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cirno=?",
      "answers": ["9", "Smart", "Good at math", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "9+0-3-0=?",
      "answers": ["6", "0390", "390", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "15-9-0=?",
      "answers": ["0915", "6", "9", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "1+0+1+Dalmations=?",
      "answers": ["11", "11 Dalmations", "101Dalmations", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "G+E+O+R+G+E=?",
      "answers": ["Amazing TA", "GEORGE", "Very Helpful", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "63-54=?",
      "answers": ["5463", "6354", "6453", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "E-G-R-O-E-G=?",
      "answers": ["GEORGE", "Great TA!", "EGROEG", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "(1+1)-(2+2)=?",
      "answers": ["11", "2211", "1212", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(5-3)-(7-2)=?",
      "answers": ["3527", "7352", "2735", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "(2+0)-(1+1)=?",
      "answers": ["1201", "2011", "1120", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "(10-9)-(6+4)=?",
      "answers": ["-9", "64910", "69104", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "(1+2+3)+(1-2-3)=?",
      "answers": ["123123", "123321", "321123", "⑨"],
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(2+3)-(4+5)-(6+7)=?",
      "answers": ["765432", "234567", "674523", "⑨"],
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "(6+7)-(2+2)=?",
      "answers": ["2267", "6722", "2672", "⑨"],
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "J+S+O+N=?",
      "answers": ["JSON", "Jayson", "JS Object Notation", "⑨"],
      "correct": "0"
    }
  ]
}
